trackduck.com 2019-09-29

# PRIVACY POLICY - TrackDuck is no longer available

Hello! TrackDuck is now brought to you by InVision. As part of the transition process, we are updating our Privacy Policy and want to give you plenty of notice.

Users signing up after June 12, 2017 should note that they are agreeing to the updated InVision [Privacy Policy](https://www.invisionapp.com/privacy) and not Privacy Policy listed below.

For users who signed up prior to that date, please note that the Privacy Policy applicable to this website and service set forth below shall be updated effective as of July 12, 2017, to the InVision [Privacy Policy](https://www.invisionapp.com/privacy).

We take personal privacy seriously and we would like to ask You to read the following Terms of Service carefully.  
By using our website You consent to our Privacy Policy if You do not consent You should stop using it  and/or our Service immediately.  
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy policy and any or all Agreements: “Client”, “You” and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the TrackDuck terms and conditions. “The Company”, “Ourselves”, “We” and “Us”, refers to TrackDuck. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalization are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.

TrackDuck collects all of the information that concerns the correct way of making Service available to  the Client, which can be categorized as:

  1. Contact Information;
  2. Financial Account Information;
  3. Transaction Information;
  4. User Account Information;
  5. User Content.

When TrackDuck conducts online research and/or re-marketing, our invitations and questionnaires clearly identify us and explain the purpose(s) of our contact. When You participate in our research, we may ask You for Your personal opinions, as well as demographic information, such as Your age, household composition and level of education. You may refuse to answer certain questions or discontinue participation in a study at any time.

We never knowingly invite children under the age of 18 to participate in research studies and/or any other activities without taking measures to ensure appropriate parental consent.  
Confidentiality and Security of Nonpublic Personal Information Except as otherwise described in Privacy Policy, we restrict access to nonpublic Personal Information about You to employees of our firm and other parties who must use that information to provide services to You. Their right to further disclose and use the information is limited by the policies of our firm, applicable law and nondisclosure agreements where appropriate. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws and regulations to guard Your Personal Information from unauthorized access, alteration, or premature destruction.

In addition to keeping Your Personal Information confidential, we will never sell, share, rent or otherwise intentionally transfer Your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address to our clients, other market research companies, direct marketing companies or any other third party.

The only exceptions when we may disclose Your Personal Information or survey responses to third parties are as follows:

  1. You request or consent to sharing Your identifying information and/or Personal Information with the third parties for a specified purpose;
  2. In accordance with the Google re-marketing guidelines, we provide Your responses and/or website-related information to a third party who is contractually bound to keep the information disclosed confidential and use it only for research or statistical purposes;
  3. We provide information to affiliates of the firm and non-affiliated third parties who perform services or functions for us in conjunction with our services to You, but only if we have a contractual agreement with the other party which prohibits them from disclosing or using the information other than for the purposes for which it was disclosed;
  4. If there would be a need to disclose Your personal data to judicial or other government institution, we would do so as required by law.

TrackDuck collects and use Your Personal Information to:

  1. Provide the Client with correct service on our end. We need to correctly identify the customer as a Client and we need a certain Personal Information to do so;
  2. Provide the Client with better service in the future. We strongly believe that we should strive for perfection and by collecting and analyzing Personal Information of the Clients we can adjust our Service accordingly.

We may provide information about You to our employees in order to administer any accounts, products and services provided to You. We will not disclose Your personal information to any third party unless You have consented to such disclosure or where we are required to do so by law. Should You breach our terms and conditions or terms of use or if we are under a duty to disclose or share Your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, we may disclose Your information to a relevant authority. This may include  exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Any disclosure of Personal Information will be strictly controlled and made fully in accordance with current European law and International privacy law.

All security on our Website is treated seriously. Where applicable, we undertake security steps, including use of SSL technology, on our back-end systems that store customer account information and to protect data transmissions. However, this is not a guarantee that such data transmissions cannot be accessed, altered or deleted due to firewall or other security software failures. We ask You to understand that no security measure is fault-proof or hacking proof. We also cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted from our servers to You. If any third party would be able to intercept a transmission from our servers to Your working environment, we would not be responsible for such act.  
We may transfer Your information to servers located outside of Your state or country, in a location having laws that are less protective of Your privacy. We are located in the European union and we are required by law to keep Your information in our home country of Republic of Lithuania. Due to the fact that we may need to transfer Your information in regards of providing You with the best possible Service by using our website, You consent for us to do so.

TrackDuck reserves the right to communicate with You by e-mail. Such communication will be strictly related to the correct way of providing the Service to the Client. The Client cannot refuse such communication due to it’s connection with the Service. TrackDuck reserves the right to send You the ads concerning the Service and/or place ads on website.  
No Responsibility for Privacy Practices of Third Parties This Privacy Policy applies only to the Service and connected services to the Service. We cannot be held responsible for the action(s) of the third party websites. If TrackDuck redirects You to a third party website our own Privacy Policy have no legal power there due to the fact that third party website may have it’s own Privacy Policy or no Privacy Policy whatsoever. The Client uses third party websites at their own risk.

This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at [the About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers

By using our website and/or Service it is possible to communicate with others, discuss in boards and/or blogs, review goods, services vendors, and submit media content. The information, including Your Personal Information, will be publicly visible and available for public. Keep in mind, that any information that is publicly shown could be used as a reading material, collected for later use and be spread across the internet.

TrackDuck allows for You to update Your Personal Information at any time. If the Client wants to delete his or her user account, even if such account is no longer accessible, TrackDuck reserves the right to keep the Client’s Personal Information as long as it is needed to comply with the financial regulations and/or needed to lawfully run the company. The information that is no longer needed shall be destroyed as required by law.

Since we are based in the European Union, we do use services and servers that are outside of the European Union. For us to be able to provide the Client with the best solution regarding the Service we do need to be able to transfer Clients Personal Information to other locations worldwide. As mentioned in Section “Storage and security”, TrackDuck reserves the right to transfer You Personal Information to our Affiliates, business partners, vendors, and/or service providers elsewhere in the world. Keep in mind, that by providing us with You Personal Information, You consent to us for doing so.

Data protection in the European union stems from a bill passed in 1995, dubbed the Data Protection Directive. This law, reaffirming European nations’ respect for all citizens’ “private and family life,” allows for individuals to obtain Personal Information the companies said information is being stored. By granting users the right to both remove and correct any Personal Information about them online, as well as by barring companies from transferring data either to another company or across national borders without the consent of the Clients.

While we encourage children to consult with their parents before furnishing personal data, parents should supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers. These tools can prevent children from disclosing their name, address and other Personal Information without parental permission. If underage person would provide us with your Personal Information, please contact as immediately for it’s removal.

Be sure to ask Your mom, dad and/or any legal guardian for permission before sending any information about Yourself to us (or anyone else) over the Internet.  
Questions regarding Privacy Policy Any comments or suggestions that You may have and which may contribute to a better quality of Service will be welcome and greatly appreciated contact us at support@stage.trackduck.com

TrackDuck reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Such changes may be announced to You either by email or by the posting of the revised policy on the Service. You are responsible for reviewing both Your own email and the Service to determine what is the then-current Privacy Policy.

Date created: _August 26, 2014_

_April 6_ – [Cookie Policy](https://stage.trackduck.com/privacy-policy#cookies) added

_June 12, 2017_ – Hello! TrackDuck is now brought to you by InVision. As part of the transition process, we are updating our Privacy Policy and want to give you plenty of notice.

Users signing up after June 12, 2017 should note that they are agreeing to the updated InVision [Privacy Policy](https://www.invisionapp.com/privacy) and not Privacy Policy listed below.

For users who signed up prior to that date, please note that the Privacy Policy applicable to this website and service set forth below shall be updated effective as of July 12, 2017, to the InVision [Privacy Policy](https://www.invisionapp.com/privacy).

Last revised: _June 12, 2017_
